datingfunda.com 2005-04-04

# Dating Funda, Privacy Policy

**Dating Funda.com** is strongly committed to providing all of our visitors and members the utmost online security by following through with our privacy act policies and practices. This statement discloses the information gathering process and the privacy and dissemination practices for the Dating Funda.com Web site. Dating Funda.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protect your personal privacy. 

**Dating Funda.com** is an internet singles portal designed to provide an easy way to meet other singles on the internet. Members create a profile and are then paired with a number of other members based on their pre-selected dating criteria. None of the information requested can be used by the public to identify a specific individual. Dating Funda does not knowingly or even attempt to collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 18, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18. 

**Public Information** is personal information that may be displayed on the site, such as gender, age and height, but cannot be linked to a particular user. Public information is personal information such as gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, and more. This information is meant to be seen by members and visitors to the site but cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, or other profile information. Members can post images of themselves but no identifying information is allowed to be posted with that image. Please note that images posted can be used by Dating Funda.com in ads or press releases about our service. People attending Dating Funda.com events can be included in photos and images taken of such events and used in ads or press releases about our service. Posting images or attending Dating Funda.com events constitutes agreement with the fair use of the images involved. 

**Private Information:** We use email addresses submitted by members when forwarding anonymous emails. Responders email addresses are not disclosed to the original sender nor is any other personally identifiable information. We may use a user's email address to send news regarding our site or offers we feel appropriate to our members but with the exception of specific direct marketing emails following the free trial period, the user may choose not to receive email of this type by indicating upon joining up to not receive such mail or later at any time through our unsubscribe methods or by modifying their account information 

**Chat Rooms, Bulletin Boards, and Forums**

Dating Funda.com makes chat rooms available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information online. 

**Use of Cookies**

We currently use cookies in our Chat areas and for our own advertising purposes. We use third-party advertising technology to serve ads when you visit our Web site and sites upon which we advertise. This technology uses information about your visits to this Web site and the sites upon which we advertise, (not including your name, address, or other personal information), to serve our ads to you. In the course of serving our advertisements to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we use web beacons, provided by our ad serving partner, to help manage our online advertising.

**Change/Delete**

Dating Funda.com gives trial members and paid members an option for modifying or removing their information from our database. Your privacy is one of our highest priorities. 

If at any time you wish to remove your personal information with Dating Funda.com, you can elect to opt-out of your subscription by simply logging in to your personals account. Also, if at anytime you have registered with Dating Funda.com, but have forgotten your login and or password, to delete said information, you can retrieve your lost account access information by visiting forgot password with the option to enter either your login name or the email address that you had originally registered with Dating Funda.com. 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy of Dating Funda.com, please contact us
